[
  {
    "quizName": "Zelda Quiz",
    "questions": [
      {
        "name": "Question 1",
        "question": "What is the name of the princess in The Legend of Zelda?",
        "options": ["Zelda", "Ganondorf", "Link", "Impa"],
        "answer": "Zelda"
      },
      {
        "name": "Question 2",
        "question": "What is the name of the main protagonist in The Legend of Zelda?",
        "options": ["Zelda", "Ganondorf", "Link", "Impa"],
        "answer": "Link"
      },
      {
        "name": "Question 3",
        "question": "What is the name of the evil sorcerer who serves as the main antagonist in The Legend of Zelda?",
        "options": ["Zelda", "Ganondorf", "Link", "Impa"],
        "answer": "Ganondorf"
      },
      {
        "name": "Question 4",
        "question": "What is the name of the kingdom in which The Legend of Zelda takes place?",
        "options": ["Hyrule", "Mushroom Kingdom", "Kokiri Forest", "Gerudo Valley"],
        "answer": "Hyrule"
      },
      {
        "name": "Question 5",
        "question": "What is the name of the recurring villainous race in The Legend of Zelda?",
        "options": ["Gorons", "Zoras", "Gerudos", "Bokoblins"],
        "answer": "Gerudos"
      }
    ]
},

{
  "quizName": "Elder Scrolls Quiz",
  "questions": [
    {
      "name": "Question 1",
      "question": "What is the name of the Dwemer city that disappeared without a trace in the Elder Scrolls universe?",
      "options": ["Alinor", "Blackreach", "Vvardenfell", "Dwemereth"],
      "answer": "Dwemereth"
    },
    {
      "name": "Question 2",
      "question": "What is the name of the legendary sword wielded by the hero of the Elder Scrolls series?",
      "options": ["Chrysamere", "Umbra", "Goldbrand", "Mehrunes' Razor"],
      "answer": "Chrysamere"
    },
    {
      "name": "Question 3",
      "question": "What is the name of the Daedric Prince of Domination?",
      "options": ["Molag Bal", "Azura", "Sheogorath", "Boethiah"],
      "answer": "Molag Bal"
    },
    {
      "name": "Question 4",
      "question": "What is the name of the city that was destroyed by a meteorite in the Elder Scrolls universe?",
      "options": ["Windhelm", "Cheydinhal", "Vivec City", "Mournhold"],
      "answer": "Vivec City"
    },
    {
      "name": "Question 5",
      "question": "What is the name of the elven race that is believed to have created the Aedra and Daedra in the Elder Scrolls universe?",
      "options": ["Altmer", "Dunmer", "Ayleid", "Falmer"],
      "answer": "Ayleid"
    }
  ]
}

]


